{"data":[{"question":"He had felt that it was necessary achieving a new poetic form in order to communicate his views.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"had felt","b":"was","c":"achieving","d":"communicate","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Achieving-> to achieve","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"Although many believed the talking leaf to be the gift from the Great Spirit but Sequoyah refused to accept that theory.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"many","b":"to be","c":"but","d":"to accept","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- But-> x,","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"In 1821, after twelve years of work, he had successfully developing a writte language that would enable thousands of Indians to read and write.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"after","b":"successfully","c":"developing","d":"would","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Developing-> developed","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"After inventing dynamite, Swedish-born Alfred Nobel became a very richness man.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"inventing","b":"became","c":"very","d":"richness","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Richness-> rich","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"Every year on December 10, the anniversary of Nobel's death, the awards are presented for the winners.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"on","b":"death","c":"presented","d":"for","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- For-> to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"No awards was presented from 1940 to 1942 at the beginning of World War II.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"No","b":"was","c":"from","d":"at","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Was-> were","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"Franklin initiated many improvement in the city of Philadelphia.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"initiated","b":"improvement","c":"in","d":"city","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Improvement-> improvements","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"Franklin played an importance role in the early history of the United States.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"an","b":"importance","c":"early","d":"the","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Importance-> important","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"Elizabeth Blackwell was born on England in 1821 and emigrated to New York City when she was ten years old.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was","b":"on","c":"in","d":"to","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- On-> in","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"She decided that she wanted to become a doctor, who was nearly impossible for a woman in the middle of the nineteenth century.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"wanted","b":"who","c":"for","d":"in","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Who-> which","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"}]}